This is Trigun.
Oh, my God.
Yes Master, I am eminently aware of that.
Let me teach him that to
stay alive is true suffering.
For all eternity he will pay for
the grievous sin of injuring you.
He will suffer unceasing despair,
anguish, wounds which can never be healed.
A wonderful show is about to begin and
you will perform as the star attraction,
Vash the Stampede.
Three demons?
Three demons are here?
Yes, this is your comeback
celebration, Vash the Stampede.
Oh man, what is that thing?
Hey, hello there!
Apparently, you're from the outside world.
We're peaceful people.
We don't want any trouble with you.
So, if you please don't...
I don't understand.
He's just lying there.
What's he doing?
Hey, you!
Get out of here!
You seem surprised.
You should know this
ship is easy prey for us.
The next few moments are likely to be the
most fulfilling you have ever experienced.
Temper, temper.
Your excitable nature will
work nicely for our game.
What now?
Alright, what's the situation, Doc?
Oh, Vash, intruders are approaching
from both sides of the ship.
I'm afraid the ones who went to check
it out have stopped reporting in.
I'm gonna do this my way.
Oh, yeah, word to the wise.
We're not dealing with
typical human beings here.
If you try pulling the
same stunt as before,
I guarantee you they will
destroy you this time.
Go stay with the doctor
until this is over.
Wait a second.
You mind telling me what
the hell these things are?
Cuz you're the one.
We should blame for this!
Get moving!
Damn, how many of these
things do I have to shoot?
I'm wasting bullets.
Where is he?
Where's the man behind the curtain?
A kick from this thing is too strong.
Concentrate.
I'm not about to trust you to
do everything around this place.
This is definitely not good.
They're going after the power plant.
Why are they doing that?
Are they trying to make
it and crash the ship?
Flash is now our only hope against them.
Everything now depends upon his success,
along with the help and strength
of the creature in black.
I'm amazed that a guy as big as you
are actually managed to get this far.
Ha!
Well, nice of you to pop in.
I believe you'll be a worthy
opponent. Hello there!
Do you even understand
the word I'm saying?
Alright!
You can take off right now!
It's your last chance!
Okay, that's it.
I will show no mercy.
What?
Well, that was an interesting display.
Okay, try this.
Say goodnight.
I think that's most of them. Yeah.
Ash!
One of the demons is heading
for power room number two.
They're going to try
to bring down the ship.
That power room is six floors below us.
We'll never make it all the
way down in time to stop him.
Hey, what the hell do
you think you're doing?
I'm making myself a little shortcut.
You know what?
Now that I actually stopped to think
about it, this is really kind of...
That idiot.
Yeah, this is a new model, alright.
Pack's a pretty powerful punch. Huh?
No, my friends can't be.
Val, Jones, Lumira, Farina.
I remember you, I remember all of you.
I've never forgotten you.
I'm sorry I didn't come
home sooner. I'm...
I'm so...
Don't make me laugh.
What are you crying for?
This only happened because
you're here, remember?
I am the third gung-ho gun,
who parted the gauntlet.
Tell me why!
Why did you have to kill him?
Why would you even want
to do something like that?
That's simple, because
you are Bash the Stampede.
Compared to what you did to July and
Augusta, this is a stroll through the tulips.
You shouldn't even be on this planet.
In fact, that's why I'm here.
I'm going to crush you
with my Poo Terrier.
Well, how'd that feel?
It didn't make a dent.
I get it.
You must be Grey the Nine Lives.
Can't exactly say I'm happy to meet you.
I guess the rumor of the man
with the nine extra lives.
Actually had some truth to it?
Shit.
Why'd you have to do that, you big dumb...
huh?
Great.
Can this get any worse?
The weird contradict is derived from
a battlefield situation when a great
spear and a great shield were pitted
against each other and both broke.
The difference here is that
my shield is invincible.
It will repel any kind of attack.
All right, let's give it a try.
That is what's always a waste of time.
Nothing can contradict my co-terrier.
I have only three important
words in my vocabulary.
Attack, trample, and destroy.
These describe what you've
been doing all this time.
Vash the Stampede.
No! Yaaaargh!
Ugh!
Ah!
Ough!
isn't that it?
Oh, my God.
Now I understand.
That explains your invulnerability.
This simplifies matters.
Hey, stop shooting!
Yes, that's it.
Keep on hollering and
making those stupid faces.
I can't get enough of it!
Is it so much to ask?
You've cost enough damage.
Can't you leave them alone?
Are you telling me that I
had this done to my body just
so I could listen to your
pathetic bleeding-heart nonsense?
You're crazier than they told me you were!
I'm going to polarize you and
the ship into tiny little pieces!
Must keep moving.
I promised her.
I must keep moving!
He's got one of fire!
Hey, snap out of it!
The plant!
Oh no!
What do we do?
Well, I'm out of here.
Damn, you're a persistent bugger.
Enough ammo!
Not good.
That thing's way too close to the plant.
Don't!
No!
Hey, Meryl, I think it
finally stopped. Yeah.
Yeah, what in the world is that it's?
Plant number one is down.
The plant is shutting down!
Is our city gonna fall?
It's just not fair. Why now?
Why in the hell is all of this happening?
It's nuts. Until yesterday,
my biggest problem was figuring out how
to get the girl I love to look my way.
Are you giving up already?
It's too soon to just give up!
There's always a solution if
you're willing to look for it.
We haven't tried everything yet.
Are you just gonna roll over and die?
Cause if you wanna live, think!
Think of what you should be doing.
You can operate the controller, can't you?
Well, can't you? Yes.
Good.
Then there's still time.
Still time.
I'm in. Can you do it?
Answer me!
Come on now, friend.
It's not over just yet.
Hold on just a little bit longer.
I can help you if you're
willing to give it a try.
I know we can do this.
Please.
What?
What? What is that?
I don't believe it.
The plant!
It's coming back to life!
Check it out.
The power levels are rising.
We're going to make it after all!
That's the way.
Take it nice and easy.
It's a once that live outside of
time and will flash the stampede!
No!
Damn it, everything happened
exactly the way they did.
No matter what you say, it's
not gonna change anything!
You better get used to
the idea that someday
you're gonna all live
on that desert planet!
I knew that it was inevitable, but I never
thought I would be the one to trigger it.
My God!
What are you doing here?
Oh no, you mean the girl we saved is...
The ship!
We're done for.
We're stuck on this planet.
Away from life.
Our peaceful days. They're over.
Damn, how does this happen?
It's flash.
This is all his fault.
That's right, it's his fault.
Yeah, everything was
fine before he came back.
Forgive me.
You think that'll make it better?
All of you, shut up!
This wasn't because of him!
It's our fault!
We all chose to ignore reality when
we knew what would happen someday!
We never lifted a finger to help, so
we have no right to point one now!
We just huddled together, shaking
in fear like scared animals!
We're still alive, and
that's what matters!
If we can work together, we can build
a decent life on this ball of sand!
Brad.
Vash!
Vash! Jessica. You're all right.
What a relief. That reminds me.
I never thanked you for
the new coat, did I?
So thanks.
It fits me like a glove.
Great.
It looks really good on you, Vash.
She doesn't seem upset
about the ship at all.
Gee, she's a tough cookie.
Needle Noggin!
Huh?
No!
Oh!
Oh! Oh!
Brad!
Brad, no!
BRAD!
I have failed.
But I do not understand.
It was a perfect plan.
You depraved lunatic!
This damn job's killing me.
Are you actually crying, Ash the Stampede?
That is wonderful, truly wonderful.
Brad!
Hang on, Brad!
Oh, Brad!
The ones who live outside of time.
It really is amazing.
My hands grew this big in 13 years.
But you haven't changed a bit.
You're exactly as I remember.
Brad! Brad!
ETERNAL PAIN
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
There's nothing else I need.
I can't see the smile.
I can't see it.
Never lose.
Na, na, na, na.
Na, na, na, na, na.
Self-protection, the means
of protecting oneself.
People expose the
weaknesses which pain them.
and thus form a group.
Before they know it, they begin to
exclude those who are not one of them.
But what becomes of those
who have been excluded?
I smiled at the children who lived in
a tight group, in their rickety house.
Sure, let's live today, let's live
tomorrow, and let's live the day after that,
even if it means living in eternal pain.